Guide to the Donald Gordon Papers, 1900-1988 UA.90.F46
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ernst Ludwig Kirchner, I.
  - Inventory of Kirchner Works, 1.
    - Farm with Group of Trees (Bauernhof mit Baumgruppe), A1 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Small Lake in Moritzburg Park (Kleiner See im Moritzburg Park), A2 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Water Lillies (Seerosen), A3 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Dodo and her Brother (Dodo und ihr Bruder), A6 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Two Standing Nudes in Forest (Zwei stehende Akte im Wald), A8 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Group in a Boat (Gesellschaft in einem Boote), A9 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Mountain Landscape near Davos (Berglandschaft bei Davos), A10 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Non-Identified Kirchner Painting (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Non-Identified Kirchner Painting (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Misc. Kirchner Painting (attributed) (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Kirchner Works; non-oil paint medium (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Kirchner Research, 2.
    This subseries includes copies of primary source material and correspondence pertaining to Dr. Gordon's research of the life and artwork of Ernst Kirchner.
    - Primary Sources, 1.
      Included in this section are copies of Ernst Kirchner's diaries and correspondence, which were acquired by Dr. Gordon during his research of the artist's life and paintings.
      - Kirchner's Letter to Botho Graef, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 127)
      - Kirchner's Correspondence with Dr. Bauer, 1923-1937 (Box 5, Folder 128)
      - Grisebach's transcription of various dated letters (Box 5, Folder 129)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grisebach, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 130)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grisebach, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 131)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grisebach, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 132)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grisebach, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 133)
      - Correspondence Letters to Grisebach, 1921-1922 (Box 5, Folder 134)
      - Letters to Grisebach, 1936-1940 (Box 5, Folder 135)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, February-July 1924 (Box 5, Folder 136)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, August-October 1924 (Box 5, Folder 137)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, November-December 1924 (Box 5, Folder 138)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, January-May 1925 (Box 5, Folder 139)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, June-September 1925 (Box 5, Folder 140)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, October-December 1925 (Box 5, Folder 141)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 142)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, 1927-1929 (Box 5, Folder 143)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, 1930-1932 (Box 5, Folder 144)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Grohmann, Will, Undated (Box 5, Folder 145)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1915-1916 (Box 5, Folder 146)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 147)
      - Kirchner's Correspondence with Hagemann, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 148)
      - Kirchner's Correspondence Letters to Hagemann, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 149)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1924-1926 (Box 5, Folder 150)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1927-1929 (Box 5, Folder 151)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1933-1935 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Hagemann, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Frau Spengler, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Frau Spengler, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Frau Spengler, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Frau Spengler, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Frau Spengler, 1922-1923 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Kirchner's Letters to Frau Spengler, 1936-1938 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Undated Letters to Frau Spengler (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Inventory List of Kirchner's Letters to Erna, 1924-1937 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Inventory List of Kirchner's Letters to Kornfeld, 1924-1937 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Inventory List of Schiefler Family Letter Collection (of Kirchner), 1912-1937 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Kirchner Diary 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Kirchner Diary 2: pgs. 1-222 (Grisebach's transcripts), 1919-1925 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Kirchner Diary 2: pgs.223-465 (Grisebach's transcripts), 1926-1928 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Research, 2.
      This section contains Dr. Gordon's correspondence with art collectors, museums, and other individuals and institutions in the United States and Europe pertaining to his pursuit of information regarding the dating and provenance of the paintings of Ernst Kirchner. Correspondence in English, German and French can be found throughout this section.
      - Gordon Correspondence to Dr. Lothar Grisebach, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Documentation Correspondence, July-October 1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Kirchner Correspondence, Ketterer, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Kirchner Book Correspondence, March-July 1965 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Kirchner Correspondence (Harvard, Selz, Dickinson Loan), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Kirchner Book Correspondence, Berlin, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Kirchner Book Correspondence, Europe, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Kirchner Book Correspondence; Munich, Nürnberg, Frankfurt, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Kirchner Correspondance, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Kirchner Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Kirchner Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Kirchner Correspondence and Photos, 1973-1983 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Kirchner Book Correspondance etc.; Schweinfurt, Ising, München, Stuttgart, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Kirchner Book Correspondence, Swiss Trips, 1958-1965 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Book Collectors, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - U.S. Kirchner Exhibition: Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Early Correspondance, U.S., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, West and South U.S., June 8-20, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Latest Correspondence, New York Trips, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Wentzel, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Mark Roskill Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Drafts - From Letters, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Kirchner Anomolies (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Notes from the Book, Monograph and Bill. refs., 1956-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Kirchner Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Catalogue: In-transit, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Kirchner Personal Library, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Master Bibliography, 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - "Insight" Quotations From Letters (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Photos and Notes: Kirchner Catalogue (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Material Not Relevant to Catalogues (photo lists, some correspondence), 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Material: oils or correspondence, interviews; Relevant 1964 Catalogue, 1953-1955, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Biographical Facts from Letters (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Article, 1904-1911 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Dated Paintings from Letters (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Reliably Dated Works for Catalogue, 1904-1910 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Reliably Dated Works for Catalogue, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Reliably Dated Works for Catalogue, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Reliably Dated Works for Catalogue, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Kirchner Estates, Vicari, Color Notes - oils, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Schames Catalogues (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Dresden Negatives and Photo Lists (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Postcards and Letter Illustrations (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript and Illustrations, 3.
    This subseries contains photographs of artwork and documents used in Dr. Gordon's book on Ernst Kirchner. Also included are several draft manuscripts of various portions of the book.
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #1-10 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #11-20 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #21-30 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #31-40 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #41-50 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #51-60 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #61-70 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #71-80 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #81-90 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #91-99 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #100-109 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #110-119 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #120-129 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #130-139 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #140-149 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #150-159 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #160-169 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #170-179 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #180-189 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #190-199 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #200-209 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #210-219 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #220-229 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #230-239 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #240-249 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #250-259 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #260-269 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #270-279 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #280-289 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #290-299 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #300-309 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #310-319 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #320-329 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #330-339 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #340-349 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #350-359 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #360-369 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #370-379 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #380-389 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #390-399 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #400-409 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #410-419 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #420-429 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #430-439 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #440-449 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #450-459 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #460-469 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #470-479 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #480-489 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #490-499 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #500-509 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #510-519 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #520-529 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #530-539 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #540-549 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #550-559 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #560-569 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #570-579 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #580-589 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #590-591 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #600-609 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #610-619 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #620-629 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #630-639 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #640-649 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #650-659 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #660-669 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #670-679 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #680-689 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #690-699 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #700-709 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #710-719 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #720-729 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #730-739 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #740-749 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #750-759 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #760-769 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #770-779 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #780-789 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #790-799 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #800-809 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #810-819 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #820-829 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #830-839 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #840-849 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #850-859 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #860-869 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #870-879 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #880-889 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #890-899 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #900-909 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #910-919 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #920-929 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #930-939 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #940-949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #950-959 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #960-969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #970-979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #980-989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #990-999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #1000-1009 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #1010-1019 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #1020-1029 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #1030-1039 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations #1040-1045 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations, verso paintings, pt. 1 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations, verso paintings, pt. 2 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations, verso paintings, pt. 3 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations, verso paintings, pt. 4 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Kirchner Text Illustrations, attributed paintings, #1-11 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Kirchner Photo Figures, #1-9 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Kirchner Photo Figures, #10-19 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Kirchner Photo Figures, #20-29 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Kirchner Text Figures, #1-9 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Kirchner Text Figures, #10-19 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Kirchner Text Figures, #20-29 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Kirchner Text Figures, #30-35 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Kirchner Photos (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Paintings to be Found (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Draft of Preface and Chapter 1 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Draft of Introduction to the Catalogue (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - First Draft: Kirchner: the Painting Oeuvre (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - First Draft: Kirchner: the Painting Oeuvre, copy with English translations (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Modern Art Exhibitions, 1900-1916, II.
  This series contains copies and photographs of art exhibit catalogs obtained by Donald Gordon for his 1974 book Modern Art Exhibitions, 1900-1916. In addition to catalogs referenced in his book, this series also contains some catalogs he decided not to include in the final published work.
  - Budapest, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - St. Petersburg, February 8, 1900 (N.S.)/ January 27, 1900 (O.S.) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Munich, March 1900 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Brussels, March 1, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Paris, March 19, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Berlin, Spring 1900 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Paris, Aril 2-22, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Paris, 7 April 1900 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Paris, April 15-Oct. 15, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Paris, May 10, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Munich, June 1900 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Pittsburgh, Nov. 1, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Paris, Dec. 5, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Budapest, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Stockholm, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - St. Petersburg, January 23-February 5, 1901 (N.S.) / January 10-123, 1901 (O.S.) (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Paris, March 1, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Brussels, March 1, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Paris, March 15, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Berlin, Sec., Spring 1901 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Paris, April 1-15, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Paris, April 20, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Paris, April 22- June 30, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Venice, April 22-Oct. 31, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Paris, May 1, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - The Hague, May 9, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Paris, June 10, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Paris, June 25, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Pittsburgh, November 7, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Vienna, December 1901 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Berlin, Sec., Winter 1901-1902 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Munich, January 1902 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Brussels, Febuary 27-March 31, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Paris, March 5, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Berlin, Sec.(4), Spring 1902 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Budapest, Spring 1902 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - St. Petersburg, March 21, 1902 (N.S.)/March 8, 1902 (O.S.) (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Paris, March 29, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Vienna, April-June 1902 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Paris, April 1, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Paris, April 20-June 30, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Paris, May 1, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Paris, May 14, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Krefelp, May 15, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Munich, June 1902 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Paris, June 2, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Le Havre, August 2, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Vienna, Nov.-Dec. 1902 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh, November 6, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Paris, November 15, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Moscow, November 27, 1902 (N.S.)/ November 14, 1902 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Berlin, Sec., Winter 1902-1903 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Vienna, January- February 1903 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Paris, January 19, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Paris, January 20, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - St. Petersburg, February 7, 1903 (N.S.)/ January 25, 1903 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - St. Petersburg, February 25, 1903 (N.S.)/ February 12, 1903 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Brussels, February 20, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Vienna, March-May 1903 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Munich, before March 4, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Paris, March 12, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Paris, March 16, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Paris, March 20, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Berlin, Spring 1903 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Budapest, Spring 1903 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Paris, April 16- June 30, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Venice, April 22-October 31, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Paris, April 27, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Paris, May 1, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Paris, May 4, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Paris, May 14, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Munich, May 30, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Amsterdam, September 12, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Paris, October 31, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Vienna, November-December 1903 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Paris, November 4, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Pittsburgh, November 5, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Paris, November 24, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Paris, December 10, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Berlin, Winter 1903-1904 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - St. Petersburg, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Vienna, January-February 1904 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Paris, January 20, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Amsterdam, February 1904 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Moscow, February 13, 1904 (N.S.)/ January 31, 1904 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Paris, February 17, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Paris, February 21, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Brussels, February 25, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Vienna, March-May 1904 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Paris, March 3, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Paris, March 15, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Berlin, Sec., Spring 1904 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Budapest, Spring 1904 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Paris, April 2, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Paris, April 8, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Paris, April 17- June 30, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Paris, April 20, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Saratov, May-June 1904 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Paris, May 1, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Amsterdam, May 8-June 15, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Paris, May 9-June 4, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Munich, May 31, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Paris, June 1, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 59-60)
  - Brussels, July 23- August 8, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Berlin, October 1904 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Paris, October 15, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Paris, October 24, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Amsterdam, November-December 1904 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Pittsburgh, November 3, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Paris, November 15, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Paris, November 22, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Berlin, December 2, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Vienna, December 1904- January 1905 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Berlin, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Vienna, January-February 1905 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Paris, January 16, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - St. Petersburg, January 16, 1905 (N.S.)/ January 3, 1905 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Prague, February 5, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Prague, February 5- March 12, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Paris, February 10, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Paris, February 10-25, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Brussels, February 21, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Moscow, February 22, 1905 (N.S.)/ February 9, 1905 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Paris, February 25, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Paris, February 25, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Vienna, March-May 1905 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Moscow, March 3, 1905 (N.S.)/ February 18, 1905 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Paris, March 10, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Budapest, Spring 1905 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Paris, March 24, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Liverpool, April-May 1905 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Paris, April 6, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Paris, April 15- June 30, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Venice, April 22, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Paris, May 1, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Paris, May 2, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Paris, May 12, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Amsterdam, May 14, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Amsterdam, July 1905 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Utrecht, September 1905 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - London, October-November 1905 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Paris, October 18, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Paris, October 21, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Paris, October 23, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Marsielle, October 28, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Vienna, November-December 1905 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Pittsburgh, November 2, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Moscow, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Vienna, January 1906 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Paris, January 12, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Rotterdam, January 26, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Moscow, January 27, 1906 (N.S.)/ January 14, 1906 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Vienna, February 1906 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - St. Petersburg, February 1906 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Bremen, Mid-February 1906 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Paris, February 14, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Berlin, February 20- March 14, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 114)